Activity: Task1 
	Token: Task1 
	Button Text:  
	Script:	Verify that you have created a security group named DBSG-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-east-2 that allows MySQL traffic. 
		Correct:	Congratulations! You have created a security group DBSG-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-east-2 that allows MySQL traffic.
		Incorrect:	You still need to create a security group DBSG-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-east-2 that allows MySQL traffic.
	Script:	Verify that you have created a security group named DBSG-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-west-2 that allows MySQL traffic. 
		Correct:	Congratulations! You have created a security group DBSG-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-west-2 that allows MySQL traffic.
		Incorrect:	You still need to create a security group DBSG-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-west-2 that allows MySQL traffic.
Activity: Task2 
	Token: Task2 
	Button Text:  
	Script:	Verify that you have created a new subnet group named DBSubnet-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-east-2. 
		Correct:	Congratulations! You have created a new subnet group named DBSubnet-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-east-2.
		Incorrect:	You still need to create a new subnet group named DBSubnet-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-east-2.
	Script:	Verify that you have created a new subnet group named DBSubnet-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-west-2. 
		Correct:	Congratulations! You have created a new subnet group named DBSubnet-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-west-2.
		Incorrect:	You still need to create a new subnet group named DBSubnet-@lab.LabInstance.Id in us-west-2.
Activity: Task3 
	Token: Task3 
	Button Text:  
	Script:	Verify that you have created a new RDS MySQL database named LabDB with MultiAZ enabled. 
		Correct:	Congratulations! You have created a new RDS MySQL database named LabDB with MultiAZ enabled.
		Incorrect:	You still need to create a new RDS MySQL database named LabDB with MultiAZ enabled.
Activity: Task4 
	Token: Task4 
	Button Text:  
	Script:	Verify that you have created a new EC2 instance named WebServer1 in us-east-2. 
		Correct:	Congratulations! You have created a new EC2 instance named WebServer1 in us-east-2.
		Incorrect:	You still need to create a new EC2 instance named WebServer1 in us-east-2.
Activity: Task5 
	Token: Task5 
	Button Text:  
	Script:	Verify that you have tested connectivity to the locations.php web page on WebServer1. 
		Correct:	Congratulations! You have tested connectivity to the locations.php web page on WebServer1.
		Incorrect:	You still need to test connectivity to the locations.php web page on WebServer1.
Activity: Task6 
	Token: Task6 
	Button Text:  
	Script:	Verify that you have created a new RDS read replica named LabDB-replica in us-west-2. 
		Correct:	Congratulations! You have created a new RDS read replica named LabDB-replica in us-west-2.
		Incorrect:	You still need to create a new RDS read replica named LabDB-replica in us-west-2.
Activity: Task7 
	Token: Task7 
	Button Text:  
	Script:	Verify that you have created a new EC2 instance named WebServer2 in us-west-2. 
		Correct:	Congratulations! You have created a new EC2 instance named WebServer2 in us-west-2.
		Incorrect:	You still need to create a new EC2 instance named WebServer2 in us-west-2.
Activity: Task8 
	Token: Task8 
	Button Text:  
	Script:	Verify that you have tested connectivity to the locations.php web page on WebServer2. 
		Correct:	Congratulations! You have tested connectivity to the locations.php web page on WebServer2.
		Incorrect:	You still need to test connectivity to the locations.php web page on WebServer2.

